865 SOUTH PETERSON WAY DENVER, CO 80223 PHONE 303 909 1532 • E-MAIL JONGREGORY75@HOTMAIL.COM

JON GREGORY

OBJECTIVE

I am seeking a position in which I may assist with the business strategies to support development of the Antarctic research projects. Over the past 10 years I have become well versed in operations, engineering, and business development of the oil and gas industry. I am confident that I would make a positive contribution and would appreciate your consideration of my skills in this roll.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2/19 – 4/20 Citadel Casing Solutions

Area Sales Representative

- Generated new and grew existing relationships for accounts in the Rockies, West Coast, and Canada.
- Generated revenue over plan of 300% during Q1 2020.
- Identified customer needs and provided engineered solutions while maintaining focus on maximizing profitability.

4/18 – 2/19 Distribution NOW

Area Sales Representative

• Generated new accounts for a startup industrial pump business in Colorado.

11/2007 – 8/2017 Halliburton Energy Services

Account Leader

- Responsible for understanding revenue/cost structures and pricing for all product service lines to multiple customers in the Rockies and western United States.
- Managed 25 account reps covering multiple service lines.
- Responsible for roughly \$650,000,000.00 in yearly revenue.
- Generated revenue forecasts for over 30 customers on a yearly basis.
- Presented performance reviews to customers.
- Established communication and built lasting relationships with customers from the C-suite to the engineering level.
- Responsible for creation of and maintaining T&Cs for all customer service contracts.
- Subject matter expert in oilfield cement engineering and operations.

6/2001 – 8/2007 Smart Solutions LLC.

President/Owner

- Started a private technical consulting company.
- Consulted on a variety of solutions to over 15 different clients.

11/2000 - 11/2001 Wellogix, Inc.

Developer II

• Developed prototype applications for a startup petroleum exploration and drilling software company.

5/1999 – 11/2000 International Business Machines

IT Specialist

• Worked on multiple teams for several high visibility projects. (www.wiredscholar.com, www.helzberg.com, Sprint.com)

EDUCATION

2012 – 2015 Texas A&M University – Mays Business School – Center for Executive Development

Certificate Program

- Financial acumen
- Business Leadership Development I & II

1994 - 1999 Colorado State University Ft. Collins, CO

Bachelor Degree, Economics

AWARDS AND MEMBERSHIPS

2012 MVP - Halliburton Energy Services

Award given by peers for top of class in Frontline Supervisor Training

2012 MVP - Halliburton Energy Services.

• Award for providing exceptional service quality to our customers.

2000 Client Team Award – IBM

Award for outstanding team contribution

1998 Associated Students of Colorado State University – Cabinet member of the year.

 Created a student body Book Swap, an enormously successful fundraiser put on at the beginning of each semester.